Yukako Yamagishi has
been in a bit of a funk lately.
What? You got a crush on someone?
Yep! And it's mutual!
So I finally went back to
Angelo's Rock and guess what?
Tourists were snapping
pictures everywhere.
Wow, who knew
that freak show would be a draw?
What's wrong, Koichi?
As long as I can hold Koichi
in my heart, I have all I need.
That's what I used to think,
before the pain became too great…
If only he'd look at me,
even a glimpse.
I'm at a complete and utter loss…
"OUR MAKEOVER WILL
HELP YOU FIND TRUE LOVE"
Cinderella?
It's finally happened!
I can't believe that catch of a man
actually proposed to me!
Thank you, Dr. Aya!
Thank you so much!
Sigh…
I suppose a woman's youth
is better spent
a cheerful troll
than a doleful beauty…
Come in.
"Our makeover will help you
find true love."
That sign speaks the truth.
If you're so inclined…
I invite you to
Beauty Institute Cinderella.
EPISODE 20
YUKAKO YAMAGISHI
DREAMS OF CINDERELLA
Please, come in.
My name is Aya Tsuji.
Sigh… Principal owner
and aesthetician.
Please don't be put off
by my mildly hypotensive cadence.
Sigh…
I'm actually very passionate
about my work.
Sigh…
You…
are quite lovely.
Sigh…
To think such a striking beauty
was hiding right here in Morioh…
Now, if I may ask you to
please have a seat.
Please fill out the form
with your name and address.
I haven't exactly decided
to go through with this.
Of course, may I present you
our list of services.
MAKEOVERS
◯ THE FIND-TRUE-LOVE MAKEOVER….........1000 YEN
◯ THE WIN-YOUR-SOULMATE MAKEOVER…1500 YEN
◯ THE MAKE-THEM-PROPOSE MAKEOVER…2000 YEN
◯ THE MAKE-HIM-OBEDIENT MAKEOVER….3000 YEN
◯ THE MARRY-INTO-MONEY MAKEOVER…..5000 YEN
◯ THE MARRY-A-CELEBRITY MAKEOVER…..7000 YEN
"Marry-a-celebrity makeover"?
My institute is a bit of
a departure from the mainstream.
I construct visages
of good fortune.
One's physiognomy—that is,
the form of one's face—
HIGH BROWS
DOUBLE EYELID
LARGE, WIDE EYES
dictates one's luck.
A face welcoming of love
will increase your chances
of finding love.
Hmm… Too bad.
Your eyes and eyebrows have
an unlucky shape.
Sigh…
I'll come right out and say it.
This is the dumbest shit
I've ever heard.
You're taking people's money
for this?
With these features,
the more you like a boy,
the more he will pull back.
Am I far off?
Is that not true?
You're totally off.
Never in my life has
that happened to me.
Is that so? Very well, then.
In your case…
Oh, you'll have to forgive me.
I haven't quite mastered
computer graphics.
This is a face that
will find true love.
Wait… Are you talking
plastic surgery?
You perform surgery?
I'll achieve this effect with only
makeup and beauty massage.
But be aware you have
only thirty minutes.
If you do not find love,
I will refund your thousand yen.
Shall we give it a go?
Yes. But nothing more
than makeup…
I suppose I can humor you
just this once.
Much obliged.
Let's begin, shall we?
Now close your eyes.
No peeking now, okay…
Whatever you do, do not move.
My hands could slip.
Koichi..
This will help me find true love?
Could changing the contours of
my eyes and eyebrows
really alter my chances?
Koichi?
I-I've been looking for you,
Yukako.
Huh? Me?
Yeah… That was you
walking past Rengatei, right?
You looked so down in the dumps,
you got me kinda worried…
Worried?
You were worried about me, Koichi?
Y-Yeah…
I know a lot has happened,
but that's all water
under the bridge.
I want you to be happy.
R-Really?
Yeah…
I can't believe it…
Could it be the makeup?
K-Koichi…
Instead of standing here,
shall we find a seat
somewhere and chat?
Huh?
U-Um… Only if you want to…
Well…
I guess I am a little thirsty…
Huh? Huh?!
It's really working.
Things are really changing!
- I get to sit at the same table as
- I suddenly have a hankering
- the adorable yet tenacious, Koichi…
- for chocolate parfait.
I guess that makes me
kinda girly…
Huh? No! Not at all!
That's what I wanted, too!
It's like I'm dreaming…
That Physiognomy stuff
really works!
I can feel it…
My luck has really turned!
I… I can't believe it…
I can feel his heartbeat,
the warmth of his body
This is heaven…
I've never been happier
in my entire life.
It's 4! How could it be 4 already?
H-Huh?!
M-My stomach hurts!
Ow…
Y-Yukako, I'm sorry!
I've gotta go home.
K-Koichi!
Why…
Why does it have to be
just thirty minutes?!
Hey, lady!
Can't you see it's a red light?
Shut your ugly trap!
It's not my fault
the light turned red!
Why's it work for only
a measly thirty minutes?!
Make it last longer!
You found love, didn't you?
Be happy with that,
and come back tomorrow.
That's what all
my other customers do.
Never! A fate that tears me away
from Koichi after 30 minutes
is a fate I refuse to endure!
Sigh…
I want the win-your-soulmate
treatment!
You can do that, right?
Graciousness isn't
your strong suit, is it?
I said, "do it!"
Sigh… Yukako.
Cinderella may have
been mistreated,
but she found true love because
she never lost her pure soul.
The moral of the story,
serendipity requires
a willing heart.
Are you up for the challenge?
A willing heart? What do you mean?
To truly transform your luck,
it takes more than
mere physiognomical alteration.
Sigh…
It was Cinderella's Fairy Godmother
who inspired me to become
an aesthetician.
Like her, I want my life to be
about giving joy to others.
You're positively gorgeous,
the apple of my eye.
So I'll do this just for you.
However…
The treatment will involve
more than your face.
Sigh…
A full body treatment…
Top to bottom
We need to create
a "win-your-soulmate" body.
And as an emblem
of that willing heart…
Apply this lipstick
every thirty minutes,
except, of course,
while you're asleep.
It maintains the potency
of the full-body treatment.
If you do,
you will have the chance of
holding on to your soulmate
for all eternity.
The price is 72,000 yen
for 24 hours.
Fine. I'll take it.
Yes… Stay absolutely still, now.
And keep those eyes shut.
I knew you weren't
some ordinary beautician.
Th-This ability…
You can see my Cinderella?
I see… So you're a Stand wielder.
Come to think of it,
I don't really care.
If you wanted to hurt me,
you would've a long time ago.
I trust you.. Fairy Godmother.
You startled me…
Fascinating. Now start.
Such a sublime girl…
All right.
You're in excellent hands.
Cinderella transforms
the body's appearance.
This is the perfect completion to
my "win-your-soulmate" treatment.
Yukako, my dear,
you have become invincible in love.
My stomach suddenly
feels all better…
Oh, this is Yukako's bag!
Whoops!
I have to give it back to her!
Koichi.
Y-Yukako…
O-Oh, yeah.
Here! I brought your bag.
Huh?
This one's mine.
I got 'em mixed up. Sorry!
W-Well, later.
W-Wait, Koichi!
Look at me.
Don't I rouse
any special feelings in you?
W-Well… Well…
Well…
Well, whaddya know, it's Koichi!
Rohan-sensei!
I'm heading to Kameyu
for research.
Come keep me company.
I really need to head home…
I can't be snapping photos in
a department store all by myself.
- I don't get it…
- Come on. It's always about you…
Jeez.
Wasn't I supposed to become
the invincible heroine?!
What happened to
Cinderella's powers?!
- Oh, Ko.
- Rest assured, Koichi has already
- Oh, Mom. Sis.
- fallen deeply for you.
His rational mind is resisting.
Did something happen
between the two of you?
That must be it.
Oh, this fine young man is
a manga artist?
- How wonderful. May we join you?
- All will be fine.
Soon enough, the tables will turn.
Cinderella is absolute.
By the way, it's 4:45.
Your thirty minutes are almost up.
You must not forget the lipstick.
I'm putting it on now.
The tables will turn, huh?
What? You're going to Kameyu?
So are we.
Huh?!
What the hell's going on?!
There are even more of them!
And his mother of all people!
The tables will turn, my ass!
I'll butcher
that bullshitting beautician!
This looks like
a good place to start.
H-Hey, are you using the flash?
This isn't good, Josuke.
The stress is making her disappear!
H-Hey, Old Man!
We've gotta get out of here!
P-Pardon us!
Out of the way!
Huh?
What's going on?
Ah!
Oh, sorry there, Koichi!
Y-Yukako..
K-Koichi…
So… the tables have turned
They really have!
Our hearts are in harmony.
His heart gushes into mine…
Nothing matters but this moment…
My new life begins now..
CINDERELLA
AYA TSUJI
Josuke, Okuyasu…
I… smooched Yukako. Yeah.
FLAIL
What'd she do to you?!
That tease just doesn't learn,
does she?
Just calm down!
It's nothing like that…
I just…
I think I've sorta fallen
for Yukako.
Wha—?
She's actually sorta started
to grow on me…
She makes me feel
all warm and fuzzy inside.
Could this be love?
- Hey, Okuyasu, did you hear that?
- I'm just so confused…
That could shock the pants
off a Stand.
He did what with Yukako…
GUSH
Hey, hey, hey!
This is nothing to cry about!
But, Koichi…
I have no idea what spawned
such a stunning change of heart,
but if you and Yukako
really like each other,
I don't see what's the big deal.
That's not it…
Yukako refuses to see me now.
That's the mystery.
She been absent at school
for two days.
She won't answer the phone…
She won't say a single word.
Nothing. Zero.
Y-You mean ever since
you guys kissed…
Nothing since that day?
Nothing.
Hmm… That is really weird.
You know, I did admire Yukako
for her unrelenting devotion.
Hate to break it to you,
but I think your only option
is to ask Yukako to her face.
We really shouldn't get involved…
Y-Yeah…
But if things turn ugly,
give us a holler!
We'll be there in a flash!
Thanks, guys. Later then.
Yeah.
But…
Damn that Koichi!
- Why does he get to kiss a girl?
- C'mon, it's nothing to get so worked up over.
Th-That hair!
Yukako!
W-Wait, Yukako!
U-Um…
I don't know
who you're referring to.
U-Um… I could've sworn
you looked just like…
No, I mean, wait!
K-Koichi…
How could you do this to me,
you conniving shrew?!
My face is falling apart!
The makeup just stuffs off!
You wretched whore of a woman!
Turn my face back!
It would seem
you've broken your promise.
It's such a shame.
And here I made doubly sure
that you knew to apply
the Cinderella lipstick
every thirty minutes…
It slipped my mind, that's all!
Wh-What's happening? My hands…
They're breaking down!
Your palm lines and
fingerprints are disappearing.
You shouldn't break your promises.
That lipstick was your assurance
of good luck.
A tremendous amount
of energy is required
to change the course
of one's destiny.
And it is no longer.
You have only yourself to blame for
not taking your destiny seriously.
D-Do you want to die?!
Die?
Ambition and wealth aren't the only
motivating factors of my work.
My role model was
Cinderella's fairy godmother,
sorceress and bringer of happiness.
It's really such a shame.
I should have never tried to
make your wish come true.
Your face and palms
are now long gone.
They have been erased
from this world.
What… did you say?
They're gone.
And this world has no use
for things with missing parts.
My face… is gone?
What kind of life does a person
with missing parts live?
Yukako!
K-Koichi!
Why is he here…?
No, I can't…
He'll know everything.
N-No, you've got the wrong person.
Dr. Aya, your beauty institute
is for women only, correct?
Get him out of here.
That's the personality…
That tough-as-nails temperament.
That's definitely Yukako.
That personality kinda
got to me, in a good way…
And that lady is
a Stand user, right?
And she did something to you…
It's all over.
I can't live like this.
I'll murder you, Aya Tsuji!
I'll murder you!
Don't despair.
That's… P-Part of her face
went flying!
There we go.
Sigh…
So this is Koichi… Sigh…
He saw through your altered state
to identify you as
Yukako Yamagishi.
Impressive… And the words
came out of her own mouth.
Some people have
an eye for character.
All right, Yukako.
Out of consideration
for his efforts,
I'll give you one final chance
as a fairy godmother.
You have one chance
to choose one of these.
Your real face is no more.
But Cinderella remembers
the face of each and every patient.
Select your own face from
among the samples.
If you can find your own,
your original features
could be restored.
Your palms and fingerprints, too.
Like Cinderella
and her glass slipper,
I invite you
to find your perfect fit.
Well, you should've just said so,
Dr. Dumbass!
Nothing but child's play!
I look at my face
in the mirror every friggin day!
But if you choose
someone else's face,
it will inevitably clash
with your own.
I take that back,
as an authority on beauty,
I can say your face
will become grotesque.
And the contours of that face
will dictate your destiny.
Y-Yukako…
Be extra careful.
Remember, your face in
a mirror is reversed.
R-Right…
The correct choice is none of them.
None of the faces are yours.
Figure that out
and I'll return your face
to its original appearance.
That is the Fairy Godmother's rule.
The more I second guess,
the more other faces
look like mine…
But…
This is it! It has to be!
I know, because it's my own face!
Are you sure?
You'll find out once you try it on.
N-No… This isn't it.
My eyes have more of a slant.
Wh-Which one is it?
I-I have no idea…
What's wrong? Choose.
No, I won't choose.
Wha—
What are you saying?
You want to live life faceless?
I'll have Koichi choose.
Because… all that matters
is that Koichi chose it.
I don't care what it looks like
or what luck it has.
The rest I can bear.
And I will live free of regret.
B-But that's not…
I don't care.
Please choose, Koichi.
O-Okay…
This is it.
I don't have a reason,
it's just a feeling.
If I do choose the wrong face…
Oh, and by the way,
that's Reverb, my Stand.
I, I want you to wound
Reverb's eyes,
so I will never see again.
You said
you wouldn't have any regrets,
but knowing you,
I know it'd upset you if I couldn't
see you as you always were.
I've fallen in love with you.
I couldn't bear to see you unhappy.
The best solution is for me
to never see again.
Koichi…
Here, Yukako…
Yes.
L-Look, Koichi!
A perfect fit!
Koichi!
We did it, Yukako!
- It's because you chose my face, Koichi!
- To think he would ask her to blind him
so he wouldn't see her face…
I figured, as Fairy Godmother,
I should bend the rules
and do a little repair work
of my own.
Now if I took the eyesight of
an innocent young man,
what kind of Fairy Godmother
would that make me?
Yukako, my dear, you certainly
have an eye for finding good men.
Beauty Institute Cinderella
is open for business.
Our makeovers will help you
find true love.
EPISODE 21
YOSHIKAGE KIRA
JUST WANTS TO LIVE QUIETLY, PART 1